mostca.com 2011-12-04

# Privacy Policy on Mostca.com

## Information about our Web site

Modern information and communication technologies play a fundamental role in the activities of the website [Mostca.com](http://www.mostca.com/).  
Our privacy policy covers Web site: [Mostca.com](http://www.mostca.com/).This statement details our current information gathering procedures, which are subject to change without notice.

## The services and links of our Web site

DoubleClick DART Cookie:

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on [www.mostca.com](http://www.mostca.com/).  
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to [Mostca.com](http://www.mostca.com/) and other sites on the Internet.   
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on [Mostca.com](http://www.mostca.com/) send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

[Mostca.com](http://www.mostca.com/) has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Mostca.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

## Automatic Collection of Information

We automatically log personal data by means such as programming or we link information automatically logged by such means with personal data about specific individuals. We do so for the following purposes:

  * Technical administration of the Web site
  * Research and development
  * Customer administration
  * Marketing

## Data Collection and Purpose Specification

We collect information from our user at several different points on our website.

## Disclosure and Visitor Choice

We do not disclose your personal data to our subsidiaries or other organisations.

## Confidentiality / Security

We do not give visitors to our Web site the option of using a secure   
transmission method to send us their personal data.

We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data thatwe have under our control from:

  * unauthorised access
  * improper use or disclosure
  * unauthorised modification
  * unlawful destruction or accidental loss

We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation.

## Modify Personal Information

You can ask us to change personally identifiable information (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), by visiting this url http://www.mostca.com/contact/.

## Policy Changes

Any changes to the privacy policy will be posted within this document as well as on the homepage and any other pertinent location. It is important to us that our users be aware of any and all policies regarding the policies for collection and use of their information. Information will be used in the manner under which it was originally collected.
